I keep remembering, crying, laughing hard, filled with curiosity, such gentle facial expressions.
I can't remember any of the most important things we did.
And maybe this is selfish of me to want.
But you're going to burn yourself away till there's nothing left.
So how then?
How can I possibly stop you?
Craig, you are kind, Sosu.
But...
But foolish, Sosu.
What happened to those two?
Ma!
Seriously? Even the Prince was no match? That's bad news.
Father...
Okay, get up, Tormentor.
You hold Reg down, so that he does not try to interfere.
Reg, get up!
You, girl, what did you do to my Reg?
Why did Reg forget?
Everything about FAPTA!
Um... well, you see...
If not for you...
If not for you, human child!
Oh no! Protector!
Gavirata!
You're in my way! Every last one of you is dead!
Oh god! Riko! Let me go! I have to stop her!
You'll be killed if you do.
But I...
Andrei!
Remembering her?!
No!
Ah!
Ugh!
What are you doing, Gabu?!
What are you doing, Gabu?
Popta, I... I exist to protect.
You don't have to protect her!
Incorrect.
Should you lay a hand on this one,
you shall no longer be able to return.
You shall also lose the Haku that is called Reg.
I have protected your future.
That big robot always looked out for you.
Be quiet.
Was Popta foolish?
Riko, blow that whistle of yours one more time.
This is really bad.
No use, she's not responding.
Prushka's also completely drained.
So Popta should've stopped herself?
Surely, there was no way Popta could stop!
It's already the end!
Mother, all of you things!
The one who deceived and stole away Reg,
and even Popta herself!
Riko, get behind me!
Are you really gonna do this, princess?
It will all end if Popta destroys it!
Riko!
There's nothing any of you can do to stop me!
Whoa!
That's great!
At long last, you're finally here!
Hey, princess!
Aren't you taking this tomboy thing too far?
What does a hollow child want with the likes of Popta?
Well, I wonder that myself.
But you know, I can't just sleep through all this now, can I?
Anachi!
Sorry, Riko.
This isn't the kind of situation where I can say I'll sort it out and be done with it.
You can leave this fight to us.
Sorry, but we have little time.
Yeah, I know.
Let's go, Belov.
This is our first and final audience with royalty!
The center mother is strong!
You are...one of those who ate, aren't you?
Very well then!
You shall die first!
It is a pleasure to meet you, Popta.
I have a gift for you.
It is something that I've treasured for a long time.
Because it is precious, I wanted to consign it to oblivion along with myself.
I wished for your mother to take everything away from me.
But this is the only thing she allowed me to keep.
I understand now.
She left it untouched because she wanted you to see it.
There's only one way you grew so big!
How much of my mother did you consume?!
Please, Popta.
Accept this gift.
What the hell is this?
What in the world?
As I meet my end...
I'm glad you are here with me.
At the end of your destiny...
There will come a time when you yourself decide your value.
Shut up!
You...
What is...
What is with you?!
What beautiful...
Eyes...
Forge ahead without fear.
I would like for you to enjoy your adventure.
Beloved, no!
Nanzufaptabigo.
Hey!
Guys!
Don't touch the perimeter!
The village's membrane has been torn!
If you contact the outside, you will disappear!
Take cover down below!
Bring Riko along with you and let her rest!
The lower level of the village will hold up the best!
And what about you?
I'll wake up Wreck!
It's hard, doesn't it?
I know that.
Carried by sense, the memories wash over you like they're your own.
The emotions...
The longing...
You can feel it wash over you from deep inside.
Well...
That probably won't be nearly enough to stop you though, will it?
I'd better be going.
Beloff told me not to underestimate the one touched by the Divine.
This situation has been chosen by him.
Cradles of Desire, the wish-granting acts.
Among humans, only children are able to use them.
The Princess carries three cradles of desire within her and is the embodiment of wish-granting power.
The conditions are already in place.
Imagine the worst-case scenario.
Riko gets injured in the commotion, and she's on the verge of death.
Then, the Princess, for some reason, perhaps to win back Reg's heart,
gives Riko a piece of herself.
What will the wish-granting power make come true?
Riko...
You're the only one.
The only one who pleads to go adventuring again while on the brink of death.
And make them all into something beyond human.
A force that will challenge the Golden City.
A Riko spawned village.
A kind of blessing device.
Am I overthinking this?
No.
He's the divinely possessed one Belov trusted.
Plus, he's one of those guys who does whatever it takes.
It can't happen.
I won't let that man take that path ever again.
Belov...
It can't be.
What a relief.
That was great.
Are you kidding me?
What is so great?
That smell is Belov's very sentiments, you know.
Now Fopta knows all about you.
So, you probably won't be killed.
However, I'm in real hot water.
Oh, and sorry, Vueko.
Which part are you sorry about?
I pretty much used up all of myself and don't have much left.
So, I can't carry you very comfortably anymore.
What is happening?
You're practically mother and child, aren't you?
Not just practically.
What is...
The meaning of this?
Hey, Belov.
Ida Miui also feels the same about you.
Must not...
Stop now, Fopta.
Fopta.
Fopta is fire.
The fire that is the successor to the consumed and desecrated.
Until all your rotten bodies are burned to ashes, there is no way Fopta can simply stop.
You're all in danger, so get away from this place.
Is that... a bird?
Do they have villagers like that, too?
No, wait!
The village's defenses are gone!
They've made their way inside!
Jizo!
A turbinate?
That's not good.
It's the primeval creatures that rule this world of the absolute boundary.
Not good.
Not good at all.
The creatures are really starting to swarm in.
Without defenses, I guess it makes for a great feeding ground.
We can't handle this.
There's too many of them.
It's all over.
This'll be the end of us.
Don't worry.
Oh, yes, that's right, Ma.
We've at least got to evacuate the kids.
What are you doing?
Those are Fopta's prey!
You let go of them!
Do not take away Fopta's duty!
And the reason I am alive!
It was Mother's last wish!
Fopta was to destroy them!
Nya!
Huah!
Uhуйте!
idades!
Fopta!
Tchamatan!
No, there is nothing left for Fopta anymore
Nothing at all
Do not take away Fopta's reason to exist
Tell me, why is it that I, even though the princess tried to eradicate us, I find myself feeling like this
So please, I'm begging you, just flee already
There's just too many of them to handle
Then why, Fopta immortal?
Is it just, is it so Fopta will suffer like this?
Hio, Kati, Togi, I'm sorry, you all came to save me
You dare, you dare do this
Can, can hardly move
Gavu, Gavu, Gavu
Fopta, my apologies
I could not protect you
Gavu, what are you talking about?
Gavu, please, please get up
If Fopta loses you again, Fopta will-
Gavu
You were born harboring a thirst for revenge
And yet acquired something irreplaceable
And called it Haku
I deeply regret
I cannot be by your side to see the reason behind it
Stop it!
Fop
Stop!
Those days I spent with you
Please stop!
My Haku
I cannot be by your side
Thank you
Rplain
Timo
I can't...
I can't move.
If nothing has been, has been accomplished, there is no value, no value at all, in being immortal.
What is it?
What is this?
Vabta, rise.
Embodiment of value.
Please.
Even if it is you alone...
Survive and live on.
Youngest.
Daughter.
Everything you can use.
Immortal.
Prayers.
All you damn Hollows do is crave.
What are you doing?
What do you want?
Please...
If we could become even just a little of your value...
Fabta always knew it is her duty to destroy every one of you.
Fabta knew it ever since being born.
But Fabta is learning things Fabta never knew.
Including the things Fabta called Haku.
There's a gabaroon that Fabta doesn't know.
A rag that Fabta doesn't know.
There was a mother that Fabta doesn't know.
Fabta doesn't know so many things.
Still, even now my duty drives me.
It compels me to destroy and free mother.
But...
This heat...
The color of this fire...
What is it?
Beyond this duty?
What lies hidden in wait?
Can there really be...
Value?
Huh?
Get her, bossa!
At the end of your destiny...
There will come a time when you yourself decide your value.
Forge ahead without fear.
I would like for you to enjoy your adventure.
You do not decide for me.
Fabta will learn of value for herself, Sosu.
Thank you.